const defaultDataLastKill = [
  {
    pregunta: "Cual es el titulo del libro?", 
    respuesta: "El Camino a Cristo"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 2 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 2"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 3 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 3"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 4 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 4"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 5 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 5"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 6 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 6"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 7 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 7"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 8 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 8"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 9 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 9"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 10 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 10"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 11 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 11"},
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 12 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 12"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 13 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 13"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 14 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 14"
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Pregunta 15 ?", 
    respuesta: "Respuesta 15"
  }
];